export const questionList = [
  {
    number: '1',
    question: 'What is HTTP?',
    a: 'A programming language.',
    b: 'A transfer protocol.',
    c: 'A CSS framework.',
    correct: 'b',
  },
  {
    number: '2',
    question: 'Who Invented Javascript?',
    a: 'Brendan Eich',
    b: 'Bjarne Stroustrup',
    c: 'Guido van Rossum',
    correct: 'a',
  },
  {
    number: '3',
    question: 'Which of these is not a Javascript array method?',
    a: '.map()',
    b: '.shift()',
    c: '.implode()',
    correct: 'c',
  },
  {
    number: '4',
    question: 'What does CSS stand for?',
    a: 'Cool Sexy Styles',
    b: 'Cascading Style Sheets',
    c: 'Creatively Styled Software',
    correct: 'b',
  },
  {
    number: '5',
    question: 'In what year was CSS invented?',
    a: '1996',
    b: '1995',
    c: '1999',
    correct: 'a',
  },
  {
    number: '6',
    question: 'Which of these development stacks uses React?',
    a: 'LAMP',
    b: 'MEAN',
    c: 'MERN',
    correct: 'c',
  },
  {
    number: '7',
    question: 'Which one of these is not a Javascript framework?',
    a: 'Ember',
    b: 'Svelte',
    c: 'Tiger',
    correct: 'c',
  },
  {
    number: '8',
    question:
      'Which one of these HTTP response codes is related to permissions?',
    a: '403',
    b: '500',
    c: '404',
    correct: 'a',
  },
  {
    number: '9',
    question: 'What would you normally use axios for?',
    a: 'To test connection to a server',
    b: 'To access an API',
    c: 'As a database to manage information',
    correct: 'b',
  },
  {
    number: '10',
    question:
      'Which one of these might stop you accessing an API from your localhost?',
    a: 'CORS',
    b: 'CDN',
    c: 'CMS',
    correct: 'a',
  },
];
